Digital Media Department Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; nam_ua395-1; 50.15 GB 36697 Digital Files
  - School of Social Welfare, 2013 October 29-2013 October 29; nam_ua395-1.11; 3.49 GB 2150 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 1/7/05 @ 10 AM Husted Offices/CTR for Excellence in Aging Services staff photo digital, 2005 January 18; nam_ua395-1.11_15; 120.4 MB 49 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 1/5/05 @ 11:30 AM State Capital Bldg Rm 331/332 Sen. Bruno's office Presidents Kermit Hall and John Ryan with various legislators digital, 2005 January 18; nam_ua395-1.11_16; 169.9 MB 116 Digital Files
    - Ctr. For Excellence in Aging Services: 2/9/05 @ 2:30 PM Downtown Campus TBA various group shots digital, 2005 February 14; nam_ua395-1.11_17; 47.2 MB 28 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; nam_ua395-1.11_18; 27.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; nam_ua395-1.11_19; 27.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; nam_ua395-1.11_20; 27.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; nam_ua395-1.11_21; 27.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/19/05 @ 5:45 PM - 6:45 PM Alumni House 5th Anniversary Party for Project digital, 2005 March 28; nam_ua395-1.11_22; 27.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 4/6/05 @ 9 AM Richardson 209 Tara Nickle with Phil McCallion digital, 2005 April 5; nam_ua395-1.11_23; 48.6 MB 35 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/23/05 variours times Main Campus President for a Day: Cat Provost digital, 2005 April 6; nam_ua395-1.11_24; 221.2 MB 130 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 5/14/05 between 2:30 and 3 PM SSW Faculty group portrait digital, 2005 May 5; nam_ua395-1.11_25; 18.6 MB 12 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 7/27/05 @ 1:30 PM Draper 116 Social Work Education Consortium digital, 2005 August 3; nam_ua395-1.11_26; 131.7 MB 93 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 11/2/05 @ 2:30 PM Page Hall Lounge Pres Hall w/ SSW faculty digital, 2005 October 27; nam_ua395-1.11_27; 86.5 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Ctr for Excellence in Aging: 11/14/05 @ 8:30 AM - 10:00 AM Empire State Plaza Albany, NY Press Event: Medicare Part D Coverage digital, 2005 November 10; nam_ua395-1.11_28; 634.6 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 2/1/06 @ 4 - 6 PM Milne 200 Unveiling Ceremony / Distinguished Professor and Colllins Fellows digital, 2005 November 30; nam_ua395-1.11_29; 428.5 MB 81 Digital Files
    - Social Welfare: 3/28/06 @ 3 PM - 5 PM CC Ballroom Town Meeting w/ Richard Catallano, 2006 April 4; nam_ua395-1.11_30; 87.4 MB 50 Digital Files
    - School of Social Welfare: 12/13/06 @ 10:30 AM-12 Noon in the Legislative Office Building, Room 711 for Announcement of state funding from the Governor, NYS Senate and NYS Assembly for the SSW's Elder Network of the Capital Region (ENCR), 2006 December 14; nam_ua395-1.11_31; 73.3 MB 88 Digital Files
    - School of Social Welfare: 5/19/07 @ 2:45 PM, outside in front of Page Hall, for photo of two new faculty members: Cathy Lewandowski and Heather Larkin., 2007 May 21; nam_ua395-1.11_32; 37.1 MB 31 Digital Files
    - School of Social Welfare: 5/23/07 @ 9:30 - 10:30 am, Life Sciences building 2nd floor auditorium for Diversity Conference Opening Remarks - types of shots: Susan Herbst, main speakers and introductions, as well as some general group shots. Point of contact: Pam 5/23/07 @ 12:45 - 1:45 pm, Life Sciences building 2nd floor auditorium for plenary session of Diversity Conference, 2007 May 24; nam_ua395-1.11_33; 89.6 MB 124 Digital Files
- Administration, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; nam_ua395-2; 1.76 GB 1251 Digital Files
  - Administration, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; nam_ua395-2.1; 1.76 GB 1251 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: 5/24/01 @ 3 PM New Library / Standish Room Agreement signing w/ Kang Won Nat'l Univ (Korean) digital, 2001 June 7; nam_ua395-2.1_1; 85.1 MB 74 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/16/02 @ 2 PM President's Conference Rm UAB 427 IFW Meeting - presentation of new leadership digital, 2002 January 24; nam_ua395-2.1_2; 625.1 KB 2 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: 5/6/02 @ 11 AM Provost's Office UAB-401 Chancellor Awardees (students) color print, 2002 May 15; nam_ua395-2.1_3; 21.0 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/17/03 @ 1 PM Nano Tech Center / Auditorium SUNY Board of Trustees Mtg. Digital, 2003 June 30; nam_ua395-2.1_4; 31.7 MB 101 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 10/27/03 @ 10 AM Pres Office Barry, Bette and LaDuke; Bob Fortune presenting check digital, 2003 October 29; nam_ua395-2.1_5; 16.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 10/27/03 @ 10 AM Pres Office Barry, Bette and LaDuke; Bob Fortune presenting check digital, 2003 October 29; nam_ua395-2.1_6; 16.1 MB 11 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/2/04 @ 12 noon CC Ballroom Announcement w/ Carlos Santiago digital, 2004 February 16; nam_ua395-2.1_7; 33.1 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/2/04 @ 12 noon CC Ballroom Announcement w/ Carlos Santiago digital, 2004 February 16; nam_ua395-2.1_8; 33.1 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Planned Giving: 4/28/04 @ 9:30 AM Advancement Office UAB Planned Giving Staff Photo digital, 2004 May 10; nam_ua395-2.1_9; 34.3 MB 23 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/27/05 @ Noon CC Executive Committee having lunch with students digital, 2005 May 11; nam_ua395-2.1_10; 41.2 MB 23 Digital Files
    - President: 9/12/05 @ 3 PM Pres. Office Mtg w/ Sen. Hugh Farley digital, 2005 September 26; nam_ua395-2.1_11; 30.6 MB 24 Digital Files
    - President: 9/12/05 @ 3:30 PM CC Assembly Hall Senate Meeting digital, 2005 September 26; nam_ua395-2.1_12; 46.1 MB 31 Digital Files
    - President: 9/12/05 @ 10:30 AM President's Office Athletic Master Plan Mtg w/ Lee McElroy digital, 2005 September 26; nam_ua395-2.1_13; 24.3 MB 17 Digital Files
    - President: 12/12/05 @ 10 AM Alumni House UAS Board of Directors Meeting - Check Presentation digital, 2005 December 15; nam_ua395-2.1_14; 178.7 MB 28 Digital Files
    - President: 12/15/05 @ 9:30 AM Standish Room Mission Review w/ SUNY System Administration, 2005 December 15; nam_ua395-2.1_15; 123.9 MB 24 Digital Files
    - President: 12/12/05 @ 6:30 PM Standish Room Business Higher Education Roundtable (BHER) Dinner, 2005 December 15; nam_ua395-2.1_16; 409.4 MB 144 Digital Files
    - President: 4/27/06 @ 4 PM UAB 437 University Council Meeting, 2006 May 11; nam_ua395-2.1_17; 100.3 MB 47 Digital Files
    - President: 4/27/06 @ 4 PM UAB 437 University Council Meeting, 2006 May 11; nam_ua395-2.1_18; 101.9 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Government Relations: 2/27/07 @ 8 a.m. - 4 p.m. Legislative Office Building and State Capitol for SUNY Day. Schedule and types of shots are forthcoming., 2007 February 28; nam_ua395-2.1_19; 21.5 MB 49 Digital Files
    - Planned Giving: 5/4/07 @ 10:30 AM Campus Center in front of the small fountain for photo of Student Award winners, 2007 May 4; nam_ua395-2.1_20; 13.2 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Planned Giving: 5/31/07 @ 11:30 AM President's Office UNH for photo of Ted Andersan, Susan Herbst and others, 2007 May 31; nam_ua395-2.1_21; 48.9 MB 58 Digital Files
    - Psycology Services: 6/13/07 @ 11 AM Pscyholog Services Center for new photos of doors, 2007 June 14; nam_ua395-2.1_22; 253.1 MB 161 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 1-2 pix of the 3 new directors for News in Photos and update Story for Enrollment Management, Latonia Spencer, Beth Post and Joel Davis on 9/28/07 from 8:30 - 9:30 a.m. in Student Services Center, Campus center B-25/26., 2007 October 11; nam_ua395-2.1_23; 11.4 MB 20 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/11/017 at 11:30 in UHALL atrium to take group shots and various shots of university president's from Afganistan. Then head over to Science Library to take shots near minerva., 2007 October 24; nam_ua395-2.1_24; 23.9 MB 51 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/8/08 @ 9:45 a.m. at the University Library foyer with George Philip and Susan Phillips passing out coffee., 2008 May 8; nam_ua395-2.1_25; 25.3 MB 55 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/8/08 @ 9:45 a.m. at the University Library foyer with George Philip and Susan Phillips passing out coffee., 2008 May 8; nam_ua395-2.1_26; 25.3 MB 55 Digital Files
    - President's Office: Photo session: 5/8/08 @ 3:30 pm for The Valedictorian Celebration in the Patroon Room (CC), 2008 May 8; nam_ua395-2.1_27; 33.2 MB 78 Digital Files
    - UPD Swearing_In, 2008 July 12; nam_ua395-2.1_28; 11.8 MB 32 Digital Files
  - Presidents, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; nam_ua395-2.2; 0.0 MB 0 Digital Files
    - Dr Robert J Jones, 2012 September 21-2015 November 25; nam_ua395-2.2.1; 0 MB 0 Digital Files
- Athletics, 2004 October 10-2016 April 22; nam_ua395-3; 12.86 GB 8122 Digital Files
  - Athletics, 2004 October 10-2016 April 22; nam_ua395-3.1; 7.17 GB 4599 Digital Files
    - University Relations: 1/31/01 @ 1:45 PM RACC Hall of Fame Room Surprise digital, 2001 February 12; nam_ua395-3.1_1; 56.4 MB 46 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/13/02 @ 2 PM RAAC press conf / Will Brown digital, 2002 March 27; nam_ua395-3.1_2; 23.7 MB 19 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: Photo session: 5/6/02 @ 1 PM RACC Hall of Fame Room press conference: Trina Thomas-Peterson; new head women's basketball coach digital, 2002 May 20; nam_ua395-3.1_3; 60.9 MB 51 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 11/5/02 @ 2:30 PM RACC Arena Men's and Women's Basketball Team Photos digital, 2002 November 20; nam_ua395-3.1_4; 308.0 KB 1 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 11/6/03 @ 3:30 PM RACC Men's and Women's Basketball Team Photos digital, 2003 November 20; nam_ua395-3.1_5; 67.6 MB 47 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/21/04 @ 5:45 PAC B-28 Pep Band rehearsal digital, 2004 February 5; nam_ua395-3.1_6; 94.6 MB 45 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 1/21/04 @ 5:45 PAC B-28 Pep Band rehearsal digital, 2004 February 5; nam_ua395-3.1_7; 94.6 MB 45 Digital Files
    - photo session: 2/7/04 @ 4 PM RACC Big Purple Growl, 2004 February 11; nam_ua395-3.1_8; 524.1 MB 207 Digital Files
    - photo session: 2/7/04 @ 4 PM RACC Big Purple Growl, 2004 February 11; nam_ua395-3.1_9; 524.1 MB 207 Digital Files
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; nam_ua395-3.1_10; 52.4 MB 34 Digital Files
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; nam_ua395-3.1_11; 143.3 MB 90 Digital Files
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; nam_ua395-3.1_12; 143.3 MB 90 Digital Files
    - Sports Infromation: photo session: 5/3/04 @ 6 PM RACC 2004 Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4; nam_ua395-3.1_13; 52.4 MB 34 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/5/04 @ 3:30 PM Football Practice Field ESPN broadcast w/ Mike Ditka and others digital, 2004 August 19; nam_ua395-3.1_14; 77.4 MB 65 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/5/04 @ 3:30 PM Football Practice Field ESPN broadcast w/ Mike Ditka and others digital, 2004 August 19; nam_ua395-3.1_15; 77.4 MB 65 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/17/04 @ 9:30 AM Giant's Practice Jody McDonald; broadcaster for WCDB digital, 2004 August 31; nam_ua395-3.1_16; 20.8 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 8/17/04 @ 12:30 PM Soccer Field Women's Soccer Team Photo digital, 2004 August 31; nam_ua395-3.1_17; 56.3 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 8/17/04 @ 9 AM Football Field President Ryan w/ Phil McConky digital, 2004 August 31; nam_ua395-3.1_18; 51.3 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 8/17/04 @ 9:30 AM Giant's Practice Jody McDonald; broadcaster for WCDB digital, 2004 August 31; nam_ua395-3.1_19; 20.8 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 8/17/04 @ 12:30 PM Soccer Field Women's Soccer Team Photo digital, 2004 August 31; nam_ua395-3.1_20; 56.3 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 8/20/04 @ 9 AM various locations Team Photos: Women's Volleyball and Women's Field Hockey digital, 2004 September 3; nam_ua395-3.1_21; 98.4 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 10/15/04 @ 6 PM RACC / Hall of Fame Room Hall of Fame Awards Dinner digital, 2004 October 4; nam_ua395-3.1_22; 227.7 MB 154 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 2/1/05 @ 3 PM PE Gym Women's Softball Team digital, 2005 February 11; nam_ua395-3.1_23; 43.9 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Sports Informaiton: 5/2/05 @ 5:30 PM RACC Arena Annual Great Dane Awards digital, 2005 April 27; nam_ua395-3.1_24; 235.6 MB 144 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/27/05 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom President's Speech to Faculty digital, 2005 April 27; nam_ua395-3.1_25; 141.1 MB 95 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/18/05 @ Noon CC Pres Hall meets w/ Betty Capaldi (SUNY Administration) digital, 2005 May 2; nam_ua395-3.1_26; 40.7 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/18/05 @ Noon Football field area Groundbreaking for Lacrosse fields digital, 2005 June 1; nam_ua395-3.1_27; 250.6 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/18/05 @ Noon Football field area Groundbreaking for Lacrosse fields digital, 2005 June 1; nam_ua395-3.1_28; 250.6 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/18/05 @ Noon Football field area Groundbreaking for Lacrosse fields digital, 2005 June 1; nam_ua395-3.1_29; 250.6 MB 126 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 8/17/05 @ 1 PM Football Bleachers various team photos for media guide digital, 2005 August 29; nam_ua395-3.1_30; 239.2 MB 122 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 9/7/05 @ 3:50 PM gym / soccer field headshots / team photo digital, 2005 September 20; nam_ua395-3.1_31; 143.2 MB 91 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 9/7/05 @ 8 AM President's Office Senate Higher Ed Team digital, 2005 September 20; nam_ua395-3.1_32; 23.0 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 10/7/05 @ 6 PM Hall of Fame Room Hall of Fame Induction_05 digital, 2005 October 17; nam_ua395-3.1_33; 329.2 MB 137 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/13/05 @ 3 PM PE Gym Women's Volleyball / the Ashleys digital, 2005 October 27; nam_ua395-3.1_34; 67.7 MB 24 Digital Files
    - University Development: 3/17/06 @ 1:30 PM Lacrosse Field New Lacrosse Field, 2006 March 31; nam_ua395-3.1_35; 155.8 MB 70 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/9/06 @ 2:30 PM Fallon Field Lacrosse team photo, 2006 May 23; nam_ua395-3.1_36; 55.5 MB 25 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/9/06 @ 2:30 PM Fallon Field Lacrosse team photo, 2006 May 23; nam_ua395-3.1_37; 55.5 MB 25 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/18/06 @ 9:15 AM Softball field Women's Softball Team, 2006 June 1; nam_ua395-3.1_38; 80.4 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 8/16/06 @ 10:30 AM various locations / RACC team photos, 2006 August 17; nam_ua395-3.1_39; 111.0 MB 54 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 10/20/06 @ 6:30 PM RACC Hall of Fame / Reception and Dinner, 2006 October 20; nam_ua395-3.1_40; 244.2 MB 144 Digital Files
    - Athletics: 11/1/06 @ 11:15 AM SEFCU announcement / ribbon cutting, 2006 November 1; nam_ua395-3.1_41; 134.4 MB 64 Digital Files
    - Development: 11/30/06 @ 1 p.m. at the SEFCU Arena, (in the training room) for photo of Ashlee Reed, 2006 November 30; nam_ua395-3.1_42; 115.9 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 6/14/07 @ 5:30 pm University Field for Special Olympics Tailgate party with Lee McElroy 6/14/07 @ 7:30 pm University Field (SEFCU Arena if raining) for Special Olympics Opening Ceremony (see Greta/Karl for details)., 2007 June 14; nam_ua395-3.1_43; 134.8 MB 239 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session; Giants Media Day Thurs. July 26 @ 11:30 a.m. behind Science Library Bldg., 2007 August 6; nam_ua395-3.1_44; 61.1 MB 85 Digital Files
    - Athletics: team shots of men's soccer, womens soccer & field hockey @ 2 p.m. on 9/4/07 at field hockey turf field, 2007 September 12; nam_ua395-3.1_45; 81.1 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Athletics:; volleyball team shot on 9/5/07 @ 3:45 p.m.inside the volleyball gym., 2007 September 12; nam_ua395-3.1_46; 19.2 MB 9 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: take shot of Hall of Fame trophy for web site, meet Brian DePasquale at 4:30 on 10/10/07., 2007 October 24; nam_ua395-3.1_47; 24.8 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/15/07 at 3:30 in studio to take shots of two athletic trophies., 2007 October 29; nam_ua395-3.1_48; 64.9 MB 22 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 2/2/08 @ 7:00 pm SEFCU Arena Big Purple Growl 2008, 2008 February 4; nam_ua395-3.1_49; 472.8 MB 174 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/8/08 @ 10:00 am for "older men basketball" at the SEFCU Arena., 2008 April 8; nam_ua395-3.1_50; 123.4 MB 62 Digital Files
    - AAU Karate National_opening ceremony, 2008 July 2; nam_ua395-3.1_51; 40.9 MB 96 Digital Files
    - Coach Bob Ford, 2008 August 6; nam_ua395-3.1_52; 11.8 MB 23 Digital Files
    - new locker room, 2008 October 3; nam_ua395-3.1_53; 54.3 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Hall of Fame_08, 2008 October 25; nam_ua395-3.1_54; 76.3 MB 162 Digital Files
    - SEFCU sign unveiling, 2009 May 13; nam_ua395-3.1_55; 18.9 MB 5 Digital Files
    - womens soccer trophy, 2009 September 1; nam_ua395-3.1_56; 7.0 MB 5 Digital Files
    - Hall_Fame, 2009 October 10; nam_ua395-3.1_57; 277.0 MB 260 Digital Files
    - Hall_Fame, 2009 October 10; nam_ua395-3.1_58; 277.0 MB 260 Digital Files
    - Hall of Fame Ceremony, 2010 October 8; nam_ua395-3.1_59; 101.5 MB 224 Digital Files
  - Athletics Portraits, 2014 March 3-2014 December 12; nam_ua395-3.2; 334.6 MB 271 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 5/4/05 @ 3 PM RACC Arena Josh Tangney / student athelete digital, 2005 May 16; nam_ua395-3.2_1; 240.7 MB 163 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 1/30/08 @ 2:30 PM studicle Women's Lacrosse / Trisha Primomo, 2008 February 12; nam_ua395-3.2_2; 1.8 MB 8 Digital Files
    - student athletes_Cushing_Reynolds, 2009 January 24; nam_ua395-3.2_3; 13.8 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Joe Reardon_softball, 2009 February 5; nam_ua395-3.2_4; 18.4 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Kevin Galuski, 2009 March 31; nam_ua395-3.2_5; 59.9 MB 36 Digital Files
  - Baseball, 2013 September 6-2013 September 9; nam_ua395-3.3; 0 MB 0 Digital Files
  - Field Hockey, 2013 October 18-2013 November 19; nam_ua395-3.4; 16.6 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 11/18/04 @ 4 PM Main Gym Bleechers Team photo: Women's Field Hockey digital, 2004 December 3; nam_ua395-3.4_1; 16.6 MB 10 Digital Files
  - Football, 2012 April 6-2015 September 14; nam_ua395-3.5; 398.9 MB 252 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/16/03 @ 2 PM Studio Football players digital, 2003 May 30; nam_ua395-3.5_1; 8.3 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/16/03 @ 2 PM Studio Football players digital, 2003 May 30; nam_ua395-3.5_2; 8.3 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 7/29/04 @ 2 PM Football Field shots of new uniforms and players digital, 2004 August 12; nam_ua395-3.5_3; 118.4 MB 69 Digital Files
    - Athletics: 11/29 @ 4:45 PM Alumni Turf Field (field hockey field) for photo of football's championshiop team trophy, 2007 November 29; nam_ua395-3.5_4; 73.2 MB 17 Digital Files
    - UAlbany Football Practice, 2008 August 22; nam_ua395-3.5_5; 126.1 MB 69 Digital Files
    - Ed Delaney, 2008 November 21; nam_ua395-3.5_6; 49.6 MB 49 Digital Files
    - trophies, 2009 July 21; nam_ua395-3.5_7; 15.0 MB 14 Digital Files
  - Mens Basketball, 2015 February 20-2015 December 22; nam_ua395-3.6; 2.58 GB 1493 Digital Files
    - DSC_0040.JPG, 2003 December 6; nam_ua395-3.6_1; 83.2 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; nam_ua395-3.6_2; 45.9 MB 19 Digital Files
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; nam_ua395-3.6_3; 156.6 MB 131 Digital Files
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; nam_ua395-3.6_4; 128.4 MB 114 Digital Files
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; nam_ua395-3.6_5; 156.6 MB 131 Digital Files
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; nam_ua395-3.6_6; 155.7 MB 86 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 10/29/04 @ 9:45 AM Gym Men's Basketball Team Photo digital, 2004 November 12; nam_ua395-3.6_7; 74.1 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 10/21/05 @ 4 PM RACC atrium Men's Basketball Team Photo, 2005 November 7; nam_ua395-3.6_8; 25.1 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/15/06 @ 10:30 AM RACC parking lot Basketball Team Send Off to NCAA in Philadelphia, 2006 March 29; nam_ua395-3.6_9; 215.3 MB 100 Digital Files
    - President: Photo session: 4/25/06 @ 1 PM Governor's Mansion Governor greets UAlbany Basketball Team, 2006 May 5; nam_ua395-3.6_10; 357.2 MB 163 Digital Files
    - President: 5/8/06 @ 1:30 PM State Legislative Bldg / State Capital Albany Basketball team visits the State Legislature, 2006 May 23; nam_ua395-3.6_11; 336.3 MB 96 Digital Files
    - President: 5/8/06 @ 1:30 PM State Legislative Bldg / State Capital Albany Basketball team visits the State Legislature, 2006 May 23; nam_ua395-3.6_12; 337.4 MB 98 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/10/06 @ 11:45 AM RACC Basketball Team photo, 2006 May 24; nam_ua395-3.6_13; 36.5 MB 14 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/10/06 @ 11:45 AM RACC Basketball Team photo, 2006 May 24; nam_ua395-3.6_14; 36.5 MB 14 Digital Files
    - President: 5/10/06 @ 6 PM Pres Res Valedictorian Dinner, 2006 May 24; nam_ua395-3.6_15; 143.1 MB 48 Digital Files
    - President: 5/11/06 @ 6 PM Pres Res Memorandum of Understanding Agreement_ East China Normal University, 2006 May 24; nam_ua395-3.6_16; 122.7 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Athletics: 10/18/06 @ 4:30 PM RACC for photo of the Basketball Team, 2006 October 31; nam_ua395-3.6_17; 42.9 MB 17 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 3/14/07 @ 2:30 PM Sefcu Arena parking lot Men's basketball send-off / NCAA Tournament, 2007 March 28; nam_ua395-3.6_18; 36.6 MB 99 Digital Files
    - Athletics: 10/25/07 @ 3 p.m., SEFCU Arena to take shot Men's Basketball team., 2007 November 7; nam_ua395-3.6_19; 23.4 MB 13 Digital Files
    - 694_5972.jpg, 2008 October 6; nam_ua395-3.6_20; 69.4 MB 149 Digital Files
    - basketball team, 2008 October 8; nam_ua395-3.6_21; 8.0 MB 20 Digital Files
    - basketball team, 2010 October 8; nam_ua395-3.6_22; 44.8 MB 17 Digital Files
  - Mens Lacrosse, 2012 July 8-2016 April 18; nam_ua395-3.7; 142.1 MB 113 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/9/03 @ 11 AM Lacrosse Field team photo digital, 2003 May 21; nam_ua395-3.7_1; 10.1 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/9/03 @ 11 AM Lacrosse Field team photo digital, 2003 May 21; nam_ua395-3.7_2; 10.1 MB 16 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/14/04 @ 1:30 PM Football Stands Lacrosse Team Photo digital, 2004 May 25; nam_ua395-3.7_3; 41.7 MB 24 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/14/04 @ 1:30 PM Football Stands Lacrosse Team Photo digital, 2004 May 25; nam_ua395-3.7_4; 41.7 MB 24 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/12/05 @ 12:30 PM Football bleechers Lacrosse Team Photo digital, 2005 May 25; nam_ua395-3.7_5; 34.6 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Athletics: 1/24/08 @ 4:15 PM, UAB Studio for portrait of Lacrosse Assistant Coach and Student Athelete., 2008 January 24; nam_ua395-3.7_6; 3.9 MB 15 Digital Files
  - Track, 2012 April 26-2015 April 20; nam_ua395-3.8; 434.0 MB 216 Digital Files